Favour Okeibunor

Frontend Engineer

Address Lagos, Lagos, 101245

Phone 909 769 1788

E-mail favourokeibunor@gmail.com

Twitter Twitter: Twitter: https://twitter.com

/OkeibunorFavour

LinkedIn: LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com

/in/favour-okeibunor-9a8461142

WWW https://linktr.ee/favourokeibunor

Well-qualified Full Web Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative Team player with excellent technical abilities offering 2 years of related experience. Experienced with working in a remote team as well.

Skills

Linux
HTML

CSS

Javascript
PHP

Laravel
SQL

Git

Docker

Programming
Unix

Work History

2020-08 - Current

Software Developer

Hollatags, Lagos, Lagos

Built the new version of the Company Website using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Laravel, and SQL.

I worked with the designs from the Product Designer and ensured the final product was pixel perfect.

It's currently hosted at https://htlnewweb.lab.com.ng/

I also redesigned and rebuilt the Frontend an internal portal for managing internal

processes. I built the frontend application using Vuejs and Vuetify Framework and fetched data from an internal API. Used charts for data summaries. I optimized usability, image upload processes and improved the general feel of the application. https://emportal.lab.com.ng/

I'm also currently working on an array of internal products using Vuejs for the frontend of the applications. These products fetch data from an internal api and are currently built to web standards of mobile responsiveness and accessibility

2019-12 - 2020-08 Freelance Developer

Self-Employed, Asaba, Delta

Built an e-commerce website for a client: dinabeauty.com.ng for hair products. Applied web standards of mobile responsiveness and accessibility.

Built a User and an Admin dashboard for a client for a farming management system. The Application allowed prospective farm investors to buy into farm units and withdraw their profits when the farm proceeds are sold.

https://dashboard.letsfarmtogether.com/login

Education

2015-01 - 2019-12 Bachelor of Science: Petroleum Engineering

University of Benin - Benin,

- Thesis: Horizontal Well Placement and Lateral Length Optimization
- Graduated cum laude 4.8/50
- Coursework in Drilling, Production, Mathematics, Programming and Reservoir Engineering
- Member of Society of Petroleum Engineers, Maths for Life Foundation
- Received National Agip Oil Company Scholarship for Engineering students
- Graduated as the Best Graduating Student in my class.

Personal Projects

- Built a Serverless Frontend Application with Nuxtjs (a Vuejs Framework) hosted at https://textguru.netlify.app. This application was built with Firebase, Vuejs and an API. It helps users extract texts from their images so they could make use of those texts. It currently supports email authentication, routing and I designed it myself as well.
- I've worked on a number of personal projects. Some hosted at https://linktr.ee/favourokeibunor.